<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="app_name">aTamilProverbs</string>
    <string name="TamilProverbs">TamilProverbs</string>
    <string name="action_search">Search</string>
    <string name="about_app">About TamilProverbs</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Type here to search</string>
    <string name="info_no_data_found">Sorry, We don\u0027t have this prover.</string>
    <string name="error_no_data_found">Sorry, Something went wrong. Please check out Contact Us menu</string>
    <string name="websearch">Search in Google</string>
    <string name="interval">Interval Time</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="seconds">Seconds</string>
    <string name="minutes">Minutes</string>
    <string name="hours">Hours</string>
    <string name="period_type">Period Type</string>
    <string name="result_str_1">You have set</string>
    <string name="result_str_2">as interval</string>
    <string name="result_str_3">You have set 00 Hours 00 minutes 00 seconds as interval</string>
    <string name="maxTimeAllowed">The maximum interval time allowed is 24 hours. To improve the battery power backup, the longer interval is recommended.</string>
    <string name="pleaseFillTime">Please enter Interval time</string>

    <string-array name="period_types">
        <item>@string/seconds</item>
        <item>@string/minutes</item>
        <item>@string/hours</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="increment">Increment</string>
    <string name="decrement">Decrement</string>
    <string name="default_interval">1</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading, Please wait&#8230;</string>
    <string name="loading_first_time">Setting up the application for the first time. This will take few minutes. Please don\'t close this application. Thank you for your Patience!!!</string>
    <string name="contact_us_content_1">For complaints, suggestions or feedback please email us at: </string>
    <string name="contact_us_content_2">tamilproverbscare@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="contact_us_content_3">Your complaints and suggestions will be addressed within hours. Cheers!!!</string>
    <string name="about_app_content_1">TAMIL PROVERBS&#0169; - FREE</string>
    <string name="about_app_content_2">version 1.0</string>
    <string name="about_app_content_3">This is a free dictionary application to help you to learn english words and its meanings in a better and easy way.</string>
    <string name="about_app_content_how_wid">How to use dictionary widget:</string>
    <string name="about_app_content_how_wid_1">&#9670; Once you installed this application, go to add widget settings and find the \'TamilProverbs\' widget from the widgets list and add it to the homescreen.\n&#9670; For the first time it will ask you to set the interval. Interval is the time frequency that how often the words will be changed on the screen.\n&#9670; If you want to change the interval you have to add a new widget. The interval time set is one time configuration for each widget.\n&#9670; The interval time can be configured as seconds,minutes and hours.\n&#9670; Once you configured the interval time in the configuration screen then clicking \'Ok\' will add the widget to your homescreen wherever you wish. Clicking \'Cancel\' will not add the widget.</string>
    <string name="about_app_content_how_app">How to use dictionary application:</string>
    <string name="about_app_content_how_app_1">&#9670; Launch \'TamilProverbs\' application from the applications menu.\n&#9670; In TAMIL PROVERBS application, you can scroll down and scroll up to see all the words.\n&#9670; You can dynamically search as you type by clicking the search icon in the action bar.\n&#9670; You can quickly jump to each alphabetical sections by clicking/dragging through the side selector.</string>
    <string name="about_app_content_pro">TAMIL PROVERBS - PRO</string>
    <string name="about_app_content_pro_1">Pro version features:</string>
    <string name="about_app_content_pro_2">	&#10003; Ad-Free &#8658; No disturbing advertisements.\n&#10003; Multi Language support - Including English, Tamil, Hindi, Kannada, Telugu.\n&#10003; Many more options - settings to change the theme, select the number of words, etc.\n&#10003; Instant support for any issues/suggestions.\n&#10003; Redirect to any words clicked on the list of words and its meanings.\n&#10003; Ability to add your own words and its Meanings.\n&#10003; Navigate to previous or next word from the widget itself.</string>
    <string name="rate_app">Rate TAMIL PROVERBS</string>
    <string name="rate_app_content">Thanks for using TAMIL PROVERBS.\n\nIf you enjoy using TAMIL PROVERBS, Please take a moment to rate it. It will take only a minute.\n\nThanks for your support!</string>
    <string name="rate_app_ratenow">Rate Now</string>
    <string name="rate_app_remind">Remind me later</string>
    <string name="rate_app_never">Never Ask</string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-5746581363497189/7559677567</string>
    
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="eula_string">COPYRIGHTS:
 
\nCopyright 2014 TamilProverbs. All Rights Reserved.
 
\n\nThis software may not, in whole or in any part, be copied, reproduced, transmitted, translated (into any
language, natural or computer), stored in a retrieval system, reduced to any electronic medium or machine readable
format, or by any other form or means without prior consent, in writing, from TamilProverbs.
 
\n\nYou are granted a limited license to use this software. The software may be used or copied only in accordance
with the terms of that license, which is described in the following paragraphs.
 

\n\nLICENSE:
\n\n\"THE SOFTWARE\" shall be taken to mean the software contained in this app and any subsequent versions
or upgrades received as a result of having purchased this app. \"BUYER\" shall be taken as the original
purchaser of the software.
 
\n\nBuyer has the non-exclusive right to the use of software only on a single device. Buyer may not electronically
transfer the program from one device to another over any type of network. Buyer may not distribute copies
of the software or the accompanying documentation to others either for a fee or without charge. Buyer may not modify
or translate the program or documentation. User may not disassemble the program or allow it to be disassembled
into its constituent source code. Buyer\'s use of the software indicates his/her acceptance of these terms
and conditions. If buyer does not agree to these conditions, return the distribution media, documentation, and
associated materials to the vendor from whom the software was purchased, and/or uninstall the software from the device,
and erase the software from any and all storage devices upon which it may have been installed.
 
\n\nThis license agreement shall be governed by the laws of The United States of America, Massachusetts and
shall inure to the benefit of TamilProverbs or its assigns.
 
\n\nDISCLAIMER / LIMITATION OF LIABILITY:
\n\nBuyer acknowledges that the software may not be free from defects and may not satisfy all of buyer\'s
needs. TamilProverbs warrants all media on which the software is distributed to be free from defects
in normal use. The software and any accompanying written materials are licensed \"AS IS\". Buyer\'s exclusive
remedy during the warranty period (if any) shall consist of replacement of distribution media if determined to be
faulty. In no event will TamilProverbs be liable for direct, indirect, incidental or consequential damage or
damages resulting from loss of use, or loss of anticipated profits resulting from any defect in the software,
even if it has been advised of the possibility of such damage. Some laws do not allow exclusion or limitation
of implied warranties or liabilities for incidental or consequential damages, so the above limitations or
exclusion may not apply.
 
\n\nSPECIFIC RESTRICTIONS:
\n\nIn accordance with the COMPUTER SOFTWARE RENTAL ACT OF 1990, this software may not be rented, lent or leased.
\n\nThe software and accompanying documentation may not be provided by a \"Backup Service\" or any other vendor
which does not provide an original package as composed of TamilProverbs, including but not limited to all original
distribution media, documentation, registration cards, and insertions.</string>

</resources>